http://www.petnshape.com/pages/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
Thank you for your interest in Pet ‘n Shape and our website. Your use of this website is subject to the Terms and Privacy Policy detailed below. This Privacy Policy is outlined to inform you of our practices with regards to how we collect and use personally identifiable information as it relates to your uses of the website.
INFORMATION PET ‘N SHAPE COLLECTS
The data that we frequently collect about our website visitors (e.g., pages accessed, IP address, browser type, duration of visit, etc.) does not necessarily allow us to personally identify each user, and personally identifying our website users is not our intention. We only collect personally identifiable information, such as your name and email address, when you opt in by registering with us or using the Website. To enhance your use of Pet ‘n Shape website, we may automatically collect specific types of information when you use or access the site. To allow us to collect this data, Pet ‘n Shape may use automated tools and files like “cookies” that may reside on our servers or your device or computer. Should you restrict our ability to use these automated tools and device, your ability to access and use all or part of our website may be restricted or completely disabled.
USE OF INFORMATION
Pet ‘n Shape primarily uses your personally identifiable information in order to provide you with access to the Website and provide personalized content on the Website that interests you. These details are also used to verify your authority to access the Website and to contact you when necessary, within reason. Pet ‘n Shape may also use some or all of the information you have provided, within reason as necessary, to provide customer support for our Website, products, and services, and to provide you with occasional printed or email communications regarding discounts, upcoming events, new products and services, or special promotions.
DISCLOSURE
Pet ‘n Shape may disclose your personal data to third parties on occasion in our sole discretion. Thus, we discourage you from disclosing information to Pet ‘n Shape that you would not want to be shared with third parties. Additionally, Pet ‘n Shape may disclose personally identifiable data as reasonably necessary in order to comply with law, regulation, or other government authority or to avert harm to yourself or others. Pet ‘n Shape may also partner with third parties who will help us provide and maintain the Website, its products and services. For instance, in the case of accepting and processing payments made to us, we will use a third party and may subcontract out production, fulfillment or other operations. In such situations, we will use commercially reasonable efforts in order to stop these third parties from disclosing your personal data, barring the purpose providing the services in questions. Lastly, Pet ‘n Shape could disclose your personally identifiable data upon a transfer or sale to another entity the entirety or majority of Pet ‘n Shape’s stock or other assets in Pet ‘n Shape’s line of business relating to this Privacy Policy or upon any corporate reorganization or bankruptcy.
LINKS
For your convenience, we may offer links or referrals to third party websites, products or services. Should you choose to visit a third party’s website or purchase its products or services, please note that the third party’s privacy policy, rather than Pet ‘n Shape’s privacy policy, will govern your activities, as well as any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.
SECURITY
As any personally identifiable information you provide to Pet ‘n Shape is purely voluntary and should not be of an extremely sensitive nature, we apply our standard security measures regarding this information and do not use encryption methods at this time. Pet ‘n Shape user accounts will be secured by user-generated passwords. Note that Pet ‘n Shape cannot assure the security of user account information. Unauthorized use or entry, hardware or software failure, and additional factors may compromise the security of user information.
POLICY CHANGES
Pet ‘n Shape reserves the right to amend this privacy policy and will detail any revisions on the Website. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Website will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.
INTERNATIONAL VISITORS AND CUSTOMERS
Pet ‘n Shape is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the European Union (EU) or other regions with laws regarding data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personal data you consent to:
1. The use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
2. The transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.
NO ERROR-FREE PERFORMANCE
Pet ‘n Shape does not promise error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always prohibit an unintended privacy issue, despite our best efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback with respects to any privacy concerns, including how we may improve this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action should we learn of any failure to comply with it.
QUESTIONS
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at:
© 2020 Pet 'n Shape Natural Treats & Chews.
